I don't think people are noticing, but the Republican Party has very honestly announced themselves as the party of white nationalism.
This statement denouncing white nationalism and white supremacy is from the members of the Committee of Oversight and Accountability in Congress.
They are the most important committee because they are the ones who do the checks and balances of the federal government and make sure they don't act up.
The statement reads,
We members of the Committee of Oversight and Accountability together denounce white nationalism and white supremacy in all its forms, including the Great Replacement Conspiracy Theory.
I'll explain that.
These hateful and dangerous ideologies have no place in the work of the United States Congress of our committee.
The replacement theory is actually a lie that has been conjured up by white supremacists and supported by places like Fox News that says that immigrants are replacing white people in this country, thus taking the country from them.
What you see here is that all the Democrats signed this and not a single Republican signed this.
Nope.
Not a single one.
You don't have to be a Democrat, but this is what it means to be a Republican.
You don't have to be a Democrat, but this is the Republican.
You don't have Republican.
You don't have to be a Democrat.
You don't have to be a Democrat, Mr.
Republican.
I'll be the Democrat.